Please, don't shoot!
Who are you?!
I-I've fled from the Empire!
I can't take that place anymore!
Another asylum-seeker?
Are you alone?
My mom's with me!
She's in the cave back there.
I understand.
You can relax now.
The Republic accepts most asylum-seekers.
Lead us to the caves.
Thank you!
But is this all of you?
Yeah, we're the only ones here.
Unless she's a particularly
full-bodied madam,
we'll be good.
I see.
It's just you three, huh?
Pattern three!
Iriq!
Turn off the light and fall back!
You bastard...
Let me go, damn it!
Die!
Kus, searchlight.
An Unwanted Medal of Honor
This one's still breathing.
Torway, what about yours?
Iriq...
Iriq, wake up.
Come on, Iriq.
Sprite, your master is...
Iriq?
Torway.
Save that for later.
He's dead.
Looks like you're going
to have to tell us, then.
Skywarrior Nihad Hyu.
We'll treat your wound,
but only after you've answered our questions.
First, where is your base?
T-To the east,
a half-day away by blimp...
Good.
What was your mission, and how
many were with your squad?
Patrolling this side of the border...
There were just three of us.
We didn't have a squad.
Where is your blimp?
I can't hear you.
You're delaying your treatment.
Along the coast once you leave the forest.
I'm so cold...
Stop... stop the bleeding, please.
Got it.
This is my last question.
Nihad, have you ever been to the border?
You can come out, Princess.
Your Highness, I'm glad you're safe.
Unfortunately, all your partners are dead.
I swear by the god Alderamin in heaven
that we will regenerate you
and treat you well
at an imperial church.
So entrust us with your souls, please.
Thank you.
I accept your soulstones.
You're carrying him?
We can just put him
somewhere safe in the bushes...
Torway,
it's okay for you to revel
in your first victory now.
So at least allow me this luxury.
He told us everything
we wanted to know, right?
How could I miss at that range?
A moving enemy is nothing
like a training dummy.
In that situation,
you usually struggle to operate
at even half your potential.
The enemy was barely moving...
Plus, you and Ikkun were both able to
stay calm and make the right moves.
But I...
Listen up, Torway Remeon.
The fact that you have an air rifle
makes you valuable to us.
Even here, that allowed me to
approach the enemy in relative safety.
You should learn from Ikta.
He knows what he can and can't do
and uses that to make decisions.
You understand Ikkun really well, don't you?
This is my responsibility.
Your Highness...
I was the one who ordered you
to see me back safely.
The Empire and the imperial family
exist to aid people's lives,
and yet we keep taking them for no reason.
But forgive me.
I must return.
I must hasten the rot and collapse
of the great tree as much as I can...
For that, I accept any
of Hell's punishments.
You're bleeding, Princess.
I don't care!
Matthew! Haro!
This blood is rotten!
This blood... the blood
of the Katjvanmaninik,
rotted so long ago...
Tastes normal.
Princess, blood doesn't go bad
as long as it's in the body.
Therefore, what you're saying
is unscientific.
Unscientific?
It's a word my master made up.
It refers to a way of thinking
that's illogical and wasteful.
When the ship sank,
I went through quite a bit
of trouble to save you.
So please, take care of your life.
I thought you hated me.
Well, what happened before was
basically just a childish tantrum...
I'm sorry.
Yatori,
underneath it all, what kind
of man is Ikta Solork?
He's a very twisted man.
However, Your Highness,
you can't build a house out
of only straight sticks.
I've memorized their names.
It was an act of legitimate self-defense.
Ikta,
please don't get depressed.
Thank you, Kus.
So this is a blimp.
Huh? Fire spirits?
Oh, when I came here
with Ikta last night,
we took out their soulstones.
You already have a plan for
this blimp, don't you, Ikta?
Of course. We're using it
to help us cross the border.
We're riding it over?
Matthew, my dear friend,
unfortunately, this can only carry three.
What's the plan, then?
Kioka Republic Western Border Garrison
So the sun rises uneventfully
once more, does it?
I'm glad that none of my comrades died,
but does the Empire have no serious
intention of fighting this war?
Excuse me, Second Lieutenant.
Allies from our rear.
That's sudden.
What unit are they with?
Well, they're all quite unusual.
I'm Second Lieutenant Nejif Harurum,
and I'm in charge here.
Second Lieutenant, dire news!
Please look at the eastern sky!
A blimp?
Blimps are expensive.
Every one of them is dear to the Kioka army.
I see.
So, this balloon itself is what we use
to barter with the Kioka forces.
Will they be willing to negotiate, though?
They'll think we're spies,
even if we pretend to be asylum-seekers.
Sure, if the negotiations drag on.
A blimp's been stolen?
We found these people and
fired a warning shot,
but one of them escaped toward the blimp.
They took the blimp?
I make no excuses.
If the court orders me drawn and quartered,
I won't complain—
Then, what are the demands
of the blimp thief?!
"I don't care what happens to me.
Return my family to the Empire.
And then I'll bring down the balloon."
So, you'll have a fictional man
making threats.
But why would we want to go back
if we've already sought asylum?
I'll tell them the warning shot
scared you or something.
What's important is how we get them
into self-preservation mode.
Send them back?
My mission is to eliminate anyone
who crosses the border!
However, consider this...
These asylum-seekers
crossed over the sea that's under
your jurisdiction to get here.
That's true, but...
If the winds above us
tilt towards the Empire,
that blimp will be gone for good!
There's no time!
Your decision, sir!
Well, that went better than expected.
I'm taking tips, everyone.
You're one hell of a con man.
You sent up an unmanned blimp
and used it to threaten them...
That's amazing, Ikkun.
He'd be more likely to heed a warning
from an ally, wouldn't he?
I'm not completely happy with this.
I finally got that air rifle
and now I've lost it.
Matthew, my dear friend,
forgive me for that.
We can't cross the border with weapons.
Don't fret over what was lost.
Rejoice that you survived.
Okay, it's about time.
Princess, you can have this back.
This is proof of who you are,
and it's about to be very important.
R-Right...
Is there something stuck on my face?
No, nothing.
Ikta Solork.
Katjvan Empire Eastern Region Garrison
Princess Chamille,
I'm glad you're back safe.
Raise your head,
Lieutenant General Hazaf Rikan.
Thank you for coming
to greet me personally.
Your words honor me.
However, I still can't believe
that after you went missing,
you landed in Kioka territory.
I only survived because
of the help of these five.
I'll introduce you.
1 Month Later
Even a life of luxury in a top hotel
gets boring after a month.
C-Can we take this sugar home?
I'd like to give it to my little brothers...
We'll get an even bigger reward
from the imperial household.
We saved the princess, after all.
There's only one reward I want, though.
Another shot at the
High-Level Officer's exam.
I-I'm sure it'll be fine.
Hey, everyone!
Read this.
You'll wake up.
The Eastern Region fell to the Republic.
Lieutenant General Hazaf Rikan
died in battle.
You should withdraw,
Lieutenant General Rikan.
What?
This battle has no meaning.
You're overstepping your bounds, Ikta!
Even when it's time to attack,
the Eastern Garrison is only defending!
Ikta!
That's because the Emperor ordered you to!
Ow...
There's no need to stop him.
I'll allow it.
Let him say what he likes.
Yes, Your Highness.
This whole war is rigged.
The Empire failed to develop the East
and wants to be rid of it.
But the Imperial Army wants
the people to think that
it was seriously fighting Kioka.
That's why a famous general's
been placed on the front lines.
This is insane. Do you
intend to accept it?
Solork-kun, I'm glad
you're not one of my men.
Because I don't have to punish a young man
for being worried about me.
We cannot withdraw.
Whether you withdraw or not,
Kioka will take the Eastern Region!
The result is the same!
The process is different.
It's one thing to obey
the Emperor's orders and lose it,
and quite another to disobey—
I'm telling you,
that's unscientific thinking!
Excuse me.
Please forget what you heard.
Take him away.
Yes, sir!
Are you trying to become
a second Bada Sankrei?
I told them...
Don't be too full of yourself.
One man's opinion can't change the war.
Katjvarna News
Eastern Region Garrison Falls
"Lieutenant General Rikan's rearguard forces
suffered the full brunt of the enemy attack
and were all but decimated."
But many of the soldiers were able
to escape because of his actions.
He was worthy of his reputation.
Every hero dies of overwork.
You're the five students who
saved the princess, right?
Weep with joy,
for you have been given the honor
of an audience with the Emperor.
Capital City Banhatahl, Old Cathedral
Alsankurt Kitra Katjvanmaninik awaits.
H-Hey, Torway,
you can't meet the Emperor's eyes
during an audience, right?
Or cough, or sneeze.
Ma-kun, calm down.
Ilf, Shohka, Echiri, your big sis
is going to do her best.
Ikta,
I'm not grabbing you and pinning
you down in front of the Emperor.
I know.
Here they are, Father.
These are the ones who
successfully escorted me
out of the Republic's territory.
Due to your actions, my daughter,
carrying the 900-year-old blood
of the Katjvan court in her veins,
has returned to me.
That is no different than
saving the Empire itself.
I shall give you all the rewards
that are within my power to grant.
Raise your heads.
I hereby bestow upon you five
the title of Imperial Knights.
We get... a decoration?
We will now have a ceremony
to celebrate your new titles.
Guide them.
Th-Then, we...
We can go to High-Level Officer's school?
It would be more accurate to say
that we're going to be forced to.
An Imperial Knight is a soldier.
And a soldier can't disobey the army.
Now you've done it, Princess.
You've ruined my plans for my life.
Your Highness, I'm grateful for the honor.
But the title of Imperial Knight
is given to a soldier.
Giving someone the title so they
become a soldier is backwards.
Is there precedent—
There is no precedent.
That's why I made you the first.
From the people's perspective,
the defeat at the Eastern Garrison
had no upside.
So now, you want heroes
to make them feel better.
That's right.
The news of what you did
is the one light the people have.
I have no choice but to
use it for political ends.
Hey, Princess.
What do you intend to do,
locking us in like this?
Did you learn to be so suspicious
from your father, Solork?
No, Ikta Sankrei?
That's the imperial family for you.
Less than a month for someone to
track down a person's identity, huh?
General Bada Sankrei,
one of history's finest generals,
who was arrested and humiliated
for disobeying orders and died in prison.
And you're his legacy.
I wasn't born from a tree trunk.
Even little "Ikta-kun" has parents.
And the man you call your master,
the first one to come up with
the way of thinking called "Science,"
was the blasphemer Doctor Anrai Kahn,
who fled to the Kioka Republic
last year, right?
If you asked him, he'd say
"blasphemer" was a compliment.
There's more I know.
Your mother is Yuhka Sankrei,
a beautiful woman whom the lecherous
Emperor invited to his harem from Kioka
and then gave to General Bada
as a reward for his efforts—
Ikta!
Say one more word about my mother
and I snap your neck with my bare hands.
That would be bad.
I'd have to kill you then, too.
This is my air rifle.
That blimp fell into imperial waters,
and General Rikan ordered its recovery.
General Rikan...
I have a message from him.
"Young heroes, I'll be praying
for your success in battle
and longevity from the afterlife."
I get the feeling I'm seeing you act
quite unlike yourself a lot lately.
Hey, Yatori.
You've gained the title of Imperial Knight,
far more valuable than acing an exam.
This is a great day for you.
Right?
But what about me?
It's the exact opposite.
This is without doubt
the worst day of my life.
It's comparable to the day
I lost my mother.
Today I became three of the things
I never wanted to be at once.
A noble, a soldier...
And a hero.
Imperial Year 905, December.
A few days after the death of Hazaf Rikan,
Ikta Solork became a soldier.
Next time: The Knights of the
High-Level Officer's School.
The Knights of the
High-Level Officer's School